

RICARDO PELEIRA WORDPRESS **DEVELOPER**

PROFILE PERSONAL

I'm a web developer with more 3 years of experience to create and development websites using the languages such as: PHP, Java, C# (.Net), CSS, HTML e Javascript. I have some experiencias and knowledgements about Frameworks (Laravel, Bootstrap, React JS, Jquery).

I'm going to apply to achieve my technical knowledgements and improve my professional level.



🕸 SKILLS AND TALENTS

- Criativity and focus by challenging problems resolution.
- Team spirit required in course of several academic and professional experience.
- Learning motivation and ease.
- Resilence in tasks resolution.

1 CONTACT INFO

Phone: 963 354 089

Email: r.peleira@hotmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ricardo-

peleira-0a73b483/

Github:

https://github.com/RickyMartin12

Website: React App

(ricardopeleiraportfolio.netlify.app)



- Portuguese: Principal language

- English: Intermedium

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developer (Wordpress PHP) Interhub (MAI 2021 - DEZ 2021)

São Brás de Alportel, Faro, Portugal

- Web developement in WordPress PHP projects (PHP, CSS, HTML and Javascript) such as: Globaldea, LetsgoTravel, Letsgo World and Interhub.
- Web Hosting using AWS LightSail WordPress PHP.

Java Web Developer (Cuba Studio)

PEPAL Intern - Câmara Municipal de Olhão (JAN 2020 - FEV 2021)

Olhão, Faro, Portugal

- Development in IT which ensures your exists system integration and was used the technology platform which has CUBA Studio and database such as PostgreSQL.

Web Developer

Conceptek a Shiji Group (MAI 2019 - AGO 2019)

Almancil, Faro, Portugal

- Web application in moodle plataform E-Learning conceptek a Shiji Group.
- Videos in E-learning conecptek platform using in golf and spa apps.

Web Programming - Intern OSEUBACKOFFICE LDA (OUT 2016 - AGO 2017)

Albufeira, Faro, Portugal

- Land Page Site's Construction using the programming languages such as: HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript e MYSQL.
- Transfers Platform's Construction.
- Implementation of Client's Transfers Tecnical Assistent

EDUCATION

Técnico Especialista em Aplicações Informáticas de Gestão

IEFP - Olhão, 2018-2019

Graduate Computer Engineer

Algarve University - Science and Technology . 2011-2015

FORMATIONS

- Web development Create 6 Projects.
- Course complete in NodeJS and MongoDB development.
- Web development using front-end such as: ES6,

TypeScript e Angular

- Laravel course